<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Sadlil Rhythom</title>
    <link>https://sadlil.com/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Sadlil Rhythom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2024 Kazi Sadlil Rhythom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sadlil.com/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t Believe in Magic.
Behind every seemingly magical feat lies careful planning, meticulous design, effective collaboration, and skilled execution. Software Engineer and Tech Lead at Google.
Currently building Software Echo-system that powers the Design, Deployment, Monitoring, and Operation of Google&amp;rsquo;s Planet Scale Enterprise Network. Software Engineer with extensive SRE expertise.
Have proven track record of designing and implementing scalable, reliable large distributed systems in cloud environments. Deep understanding of best practices for ensuring the availability and performance of mission-critical systems at scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiences</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/works/</guid>
      <description>Senior Software Engineer, Tech Lead Google, Ireland.   March 2023 – Present  Full Time  Golang Tech Lead Software Architecture Intent Driven Networking  Leading the Software and automation echo-system to ensure Security, Safety and Compliance of Google&amp;rsquo;s Planet Scale Enterprise Networking.   
Software Engineer, Tech Lead - Google Enterprise Network Google, Ireland.   April 2022 – Feb 2023  Full Time  Golang Tech Lead Software Architecture  Software Engineer and Tech Lead at Google Enterprise Networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/skills/</guid>
      <description>Go C++  gRPC Protocol Buffer Docker Kubernetes GCP AWS  ElasticSearch MySQL PostgreSQL Presto Kafka SQS  Prometheus Grafana Loki  Software Architecture Software Desing  Software Defined Networking Intent Driven Networking  Technical Leadership Mentoring Teaching   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/blogs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>                              </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>