<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Sadlil&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://sadlil.com/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Sadlil&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Kazi Sadlil Rhythom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sadlil.com/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer and Tech Lead at Google. Building Software to Automate Network Design, Delivery and Monitoring at Planet Scale.
Has experience in designing and building highly scalable and reliable distributed systems, utilizing cloud computing technologies, and optimizing low latency communication. Software Engineer but with a extensive SRE mindset, keeping up with the best practices in ensuring the availability and performance of large-scale systems.
 Personality ENTJ-A (The Commander)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiences</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/works/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer, Tech Lead - Global Networking Google, Ireland.
 May 2022 – Present  Full Time  Go Software Defined Networking  Working to Deliver Google&amp;rsquo;s NextGEN Global Networking Backbone. After several years working as a Site Reliability Engineer, moved back to doing Software Engineering again. Building Software to Automatically Design, Deploy and Monitor Planet Scale Software Defined Networks for Google Global Networking.   - - -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/skills/</guid>
      <description>Go C++ Python  Docker Kubernetes  ElasticSearch MySQL PgSQL Presto  GCP AWS  gRPC Protocol Buffer  Kafka SQS  Prometheus Grafana Loki    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/blogs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/achievements/</guid>
      <description>2022  Became Tech Lead of Network Delivery Team - Designing software to automate delivery of Planet Scale Network  Changed Role to be a Software Engineer for Google Global Networking Team
 2020  Joined Google As a Software Engineer, Site Reliability Engineering - Managing Google&amp;rsquo;s authentication and authorization Infra  Moved to Dublin, Ireland
 2019  Joined Booking.com As a Site Reliability Engineer - Working on multi cloud and bare metal kubernetes container architecture  Moved to Amsterdam, Netherlands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sadlil.com/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sadlil.com/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>                               </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>